Guide to the Computational Engineering Building (Duncan Hall) Construction records, 1981-2002 UA 366
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
Computational Engineering Building (Duncan Hall) Construction records
1992-1996
1981-2002
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas https://library.rice.edu/woodson
Rice University
UA 366
2195
20 Linear Feet 23 boxes plus 6 drawers
The Computational Engineering Building (Duncan Hall) Construction records is comprised of submittals, project manager files, material samples, specifications, and drawings from the planning and construction of Duncan Hall. Duncan Hall is the home of several math, science, and engineering departments at Rice University, including the George R. Brown school of Engineering, Computational and Applied Mathematics, Computer Science, and Statistics. The building was designed by British architect John Outram and constructed between 1994 and 1996.
Biographical / Historical
The Rice Board of Governors approved the construction of Duncan Hall in 1993. Ken Kennedy, the director of the Center for Research on Parallel Computation, a consortium headquartered at Rice, said, "Computational Engineering is vital to the future of Rice and the nation." The building was designed to be a state-of-the-art facility for computation engineering. The goal was to bring together several related fields in Computational Engineering and foster collaboration between them. Rice received submissions from hundreds of firms, but ultimately selected British architect John Outram. Outram's design and approach were unorthodox and exciting but also stirred some controversy. He imbued his design elements with a rich if esoteric symbology and meaning. Outram wrote extensively about the philosophy and symbolism behind the building's elaborate and colorful design, and his essays can be found be found on his website. The budget for the project was set at $16.5 million. The Groundbreaking Ceremony was held on November 4th, 1994, and featured an exhibition of robots built by grade school students. Construction was completed late in 1996 and the building opened on November 4th. The building is named after Anne and Charles Duncan, Jr. Charles was a former chairman of the University's Board. Duncan Hall is currently a flagship building for the George R. Brown School of Engineering, and houses the departments of Computational and Applied Mathematics (CAAM), Computer Science (COMP), Statistics (STAT), part of the Department of Electrical and Computer Engineering (ECE), the Ken Kennedy Institute for Information Technology, and the offices of the Dean of Engineering.
For more information, visit Dr. Keith Cooper's Unofficial Duncan Hall Website, the Computer Science Department's facilities web page, and the website of John Outram and Associates
Scope and Contents
The Computational Engineering Building Construction records are comprised of the records, drawings, manuals, correspondence, and samples generated during the planning and construction of Duncan Hall between 1992 and 1996. Submittals of plans and material samples from contractors comprises the largest portion of the collection. These records include transmittals and other correspondence. The second large portion is the project manager's alphabetical files, which includes correspondence with contractors and the university, photographs, and some drawings. The collection also contains a large selection of civil, architectural, structural, and mechanical/electric drawings and schematics. Smaller portions include the building manuals, meeting minutes and schedules.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Transferred from Duncan Hall, summer of 2015, by Dr. Keith D. Cooper, faculty representative of the Duncan Hall design team.
Conditions Governing Access
Stored off-site at the Library Service Center. Please request this material via woodson@rice.edu or call 713-348-2586.
Index Terms
Subjects
Architecture -- Texas -- Houston -- 20th century; Rice University -- History; Architecture; Architecture, American; Universities and colleges
Document Types
photographs; architectural drawings (visual works); letters (correspondence)
Subjects (Persons)
Cooper, Keith; Outram, John
- Submittals (by Construction Division), 1994-1996
  - Division 02: Site Construction
    - 02376
      - 02376-01A: Texas Cold Finished Steel, Inc., 2/16/1995 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - 02515
      - 02515-01A: American Marble, Brick Paver Sample, 10/13/1995 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - 02515-02A: American Marble, 11/28/1995 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - 02515-03A: American Marble, Paver and Grout Samples, 12/15/1995 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - 02614
      - 02614-01A, Lott Builders, 6/19/1996 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - 02480
      - 02840-01A: Pioneer Concrete, 5/31/1996 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - 02840-02A: Lott Builders, 8/28/1996 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Division 03: Concrete
    - 03100
      - 03100-01A: Burke-Dayton Concrete, 3/15/1995 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - 03100-02A: Burke-Dayton Concrete, 3/15/1995 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - 03100-03A: Burke-Dayton Concrete, 4/26/1995 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - 03100-04A: Lott Builders, 6/23/1995 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - 03200
      - 03200-01A: Texas Cold Finished Steel, 1-2/1995 (Box 1, Folder 12)
      - 03200-02A: Texas Cold Finished Steel, 3/1995 (Box 1, Folder 13)
        - Grade Beams, Pour #1, Sheet 1, P 1, 3/2/1995 (Drawer 174, Folder 1-2)
      - 03200-03A: Texas Cold Finished Steel, 3/1995 (Box 1, Folder 14)
      - 03200-04A: Texas Cold Finished Steel, 4/14/1995 (Box 1, Folder 15)
      - 03200-05A: Texas Cold Finished Steel, 4/19/1995 (Box 1, Folder 16)
      - 03200-06A: Texas Cold Finished Steel, 4/1995 (Box 1, Folder 17)
        - Drawing: Grade Beam Pour #2, S1, P6, 4/3/1995 (Drawer 174, Folder 1, Page 3)
      - 03200-07A: Texas Cold Finished Steel, 5/1995 (Box 1, Folder 18)
      - 03200-08A: Texas Cold Finished Steel, 5/1995 (Box 1, Folder 19)
        - Drawing: Ground Floor Slab, S10, P8 (2 copies), 5/11/1995 (Drawer 174, Folder 1, Page 4-5)
      - 03200-09A: Texas Cold Finished Steel, 5/1995 (Box 1, Folder 20)
      - 03200-10A: Texas Cold Finished Steel, 7/1995 (Box 1, Folder 21)
        - Drawing: Second Floor Framing (Partial), 1-8, S-11 to S12, P9 (2 copies), 6/28/1995 (Drawer 174, Folder 1, Page 6-7)
      - 03200-11A: Texas Cold Finished Steel, 8/1995 (Box 1, Folder 22)
        - Drawing: Partial Second Floor Framing, Slab 9-20, S23, P14 (2 copies), 7/20/1995 (Drawer 174, Folder 1, Page 8-9)
      - 03200-12A: Texas Cold Finished Steel, 8/1995 (Box 1, Folder 23)
        - Drawings: COLS SUPT Lvl 2-4, COLS, P10 (2 copies), 8/11/1995 (Drawer 174, Folder 1, Page 10a-10c; 11a-11c)
      - 03200-13A: Texas Cold Finished Steel, 9/1995 (Box 1, Folder 24)
      - 03200-14A: Texas Cold Finished Steel, 9/1995 (Box 1, Folder 25)
      - 03200-15A: Texas Cold Finished Steel, 9/1995 (Box 1, Folder 26)
      - 03200-16A: Texas Cold Finished Steel, 9/1995 (Box 1, Folder 27)
      - 03200-17A: Texas Cold Finished Steel, 10/1995 (Box 1, Folder 28)
        - Drawing: 3rd Floor 9-20, S24/S25, P15 ( 2 copies), 9/25/1995 (Drawer 174, Folder 1, Page 12-13)
      - 03200-18A: Texas Cold Finished Steel, 10/1995 (Box 1, Folder 29)
        - Drawing: 4th Floor 9-20; S26/S27, P16 (2 copies), 7/10/1995 (Drawer 174, Folder 1, Page 14-15)
    - 03300
      - 03300-01A: Concrete Mix Design, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 30)
      - 03300-02A: Concrete Mix Design, 1/1995 (Box 1, Folder 31)
      - 03300-03A: Pioneer Concrete, 3/1995 (Box 1, Folder 32)
      - 03300-04A: Synko Flex Water Stop, 3/1995 (Box 1, Folder 33)
      - 03300-05A: Pioneer Concrete, 8/1995 (Box 1, Folder 34)
      - 03300-06A: Lott Builders, 3/1996 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - 03365
      - 03365-01A: Suncoast, 9/19/1995 (Box 1, Folder 36)
        - Post-Tension Drawings PT-1, PT-2, & PT-3 (2 sets of 3 pages), 8/14/1995 (Drawer 174, Folder 1, Page 17-21)
      - 03365-01B: Suncoast, 8-10/1995 (Box 1, Folder 37)
        - Drawing: Honeycomb @ Beam Anchorage, Monostrand Anchor, Stress Ram, 9/27/1995 (Drawer 174, Folder 1, Page 22-24)
      - 03365-01C: Suncoast, 10/1995 (Box 1, Folder 38)
        - Drawing: End Anchor Details, PT-3, 10/16/1995 (Drawer 174, Folder 1, Page 25)
      - 03365-02A: Suncoast, 9/1995 (Box 1, Folder 39)
      - 03365-03A: Suncoast, 8-9/1995 (Box 1, Folder 40)
      - 03365-04A: Lott Builders, 11-12/1995 (Box 1, Folder 41)
      - 03365-05A: Maxim, 12/1995 (Box 1, Folder 42)
      - 03365-06A: Suncoast, 12/1995 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - 03450
      - 03450-01A Hakco, 3/1995 (Box 1, Folder 44)
      - 03450-01B Hakco, 4/1995 (Box 1, Folder 45)
      - 03450-02A Hakco, 3/1995 (Box 1, Folder 46)
        - Drawings: Arch. Precast Pieces: PC-001, 002, 201-204, 301-303, 320-321, 401-403, 2/2/1995 (Drawer 174, Folder 2, Page 1-2)
      - 03450-02B Hakco, 5/1995 (Box 1, Folder 47)
        - Arch. Precast Drawings: PC-001, 002, 201-204, 301-304, 4/21/1995 (Drawer 174, Folder 2, Page 3)
      - 03450-02C Hakco, 6/1995 (Box 1, Folder 48)
      - 03450-03A Hakco, 3/1995 (Box 1, Folder 49)
        - Arch. Precast Drawings: PC-404-406 (2 Sets), 3/9/1995 (Drawer 174, Folder 2, Page 4-5)
      - 03450-03B Hakco, 5/1995 (Box 1, Folder 50)
        - Arch. Precast Drawings: PC-404-406, 3/9/1995 (Drawer 174, Folder 2, Page 6-7)
      - 03450-03C Hakco, 7/1995 (Box 1, Folder 51)
        - Arch Precast Drawings: PC-001-002; 404-405, 2/2/1995 (Drawer 174, Folder 2, Page 8-9)
      - 03450-04A Hakco, 4/1995 (Box 1, Folder 52)
      - 03450-04B Hakco, 7/1995 (Box 1, Folder 53)
      - 03450-05A Hakco, 7/1995 (Box 1, Folder 54)
      - 03450-05B Hakco, 8/1995 (Box 1, Folder 55)
      - 03450-06A Hakco, 7/1995 (Box 1, Folder 56)
      - 03450-06B Hakco, 7/1995 (Box 1, Folder 57)
      - 03450-07A Hakco, 5/1995 (Box 1, Folder 58)
      - 03450-07B Hakco, 7/1995 (Box 1, Folder 59)
      - 03450-07C Hakco, 8/1995 (Box 1, Folder 60)
      - 03450-07D Hakco, 11/1995 (Box 1, Folder 61)
      - 03450-07E Hakco, 11/1995 (Box 1, Folder 62)
      - 03450-08A Hakco, 7/1995 (Box 1, Folder 63)
      - 03450-08B Hakco, 6/1995 (Box 1, Folder 64)
      - 03450-08C Hakco, 7/1995 (Box 1, Folder 65)
      - 03450-08D Hakco, 8/1995 (Box 1, Folder 66)
      - 03450-09A Hakco, 6/1995 (Box 1, Folder 67)
      - 03450-09B Hakco, 8/1995 (Box 1, Folder 68)
      - 03450-10A-10B Hakco, 6/1995 (Box 1, Folder 69)
        - Arch Precast Structural Drawings: PC-001-003, 211, 325-328, 330, 403, 407-410, 2/2/1995 (Drawer 174, Folder 2, Page 10)
        - 03450-10B: Arch Precast Structural Drawings: PC-003, 211, 325, 409-410, 2/2/1995 (Drawer 174, Folder 2, Page 11)
      - 03450-10B Hakco, 8/1995 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - 03450-11A Hakco, 7/1995 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      - 03450-12A Hakco, 8/1995 (Box 2, Folder 3)
        - 03450-12A: Arch Precast Structural Drawings: PC-130-134, 212-214, 329, 333, 333.1-333.3, 334, 335, 6/6/1995 (Drawer 174, Folder 2, Page 12)
        - 03450-12A: Arch Precast Structural Drawings: PC-002, 003, 110-121, 206-210, 307-319, 3/28/1996 (Drawer 174, Folder 2, Page 13)
      - 03450-13A Hakco, 7/1995 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - 03450-13B Hakco, 7/1995 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - 03450-13C Hakco, 7/1995 (Box 2, Folder 6)
      - 03450-13D Hakco, 8/1995 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - 03450-13E Hakco, 10/1995 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      - 03450-13F Hakco, 11/1995 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      - 03450-13G Hakco, 11/1995 (Box 2, Folder 10)
      - 03450-13H Hakco, 11/1995 (Box 2, Folder 11)
      - 03450-13I Hakco, 12/1995 (Box 2, Folder 12)
      - 03450-14A Hakco, 8/1995 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      - 03450-15A Hakco, 6/1995 (Box 2, Folder 14)
      - 03450-16A Hakco, 6/1995 (Box 2, Folder 15)
      - 03450-17A-29A Hakco, 6/1995-7/1995 (Box 2, Folder 16)
      - 03450-30A-30B Hakco, 7/1995 (Box 2, Folder 17)
      - 03450-31A-31F Hakco, 6/1995-10/1995 (Box 2, Folder 18)
      - 03450-32A Hakco, 7/1995 (Box 2, Folder 19)
      - 03450-33A-33B Hakco, 9-11/1995 (Box 2, Folder 20)
      - 03450-34A Hakco, 10/1995 (Box 2, Folder 21)
        - 03450-34A: Arch Precast Structural Drawings: PC-004, PC-135-143 (2 Sets), 9/15/1995 (Drawer 174, Folder 2, Page 14-15)
      - 03450-35A Hakco, 10/1995 (Box 2, Folder 22)
      - 03450-35B Chamberlain, 7/1996 (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - 03450-36A Hacko, 10/1995 (Box 2, Folder 24)
        - 03450-36A: Arch Precast Structural Drawings: PC-002, 004.1, 215, 330, 330.1-330.4, 336-339, 406, 8/24/1995 (Drawer 174, Folder 2, Page 16)
      - 03450-37A Hacko, 11/1995 (Box 2, Folder 25)
        - 03450-37A: Arch Precast Drawings: PC-205, 356, 363, 364, 368, 414, 10/26/1995 (Drawer 174, Folder 2, Page 17)
      - 03450-38A-41A Hacko, 11/1995-3/1996 (Box 2, Folder 26)
        - 03450-38A: Arch Precast Drawings: PC-002.1, 004, 206, 213, 215, 340, 341, 344-346, 355, 360, 408, 411, 10/11/1995 (Drawer 174, Folder 2, Page 18)
        - 03450-38A: Arch Precast Drawings: PC-002, 004.1, 215, 330, 330.1-330.4, 336-339, 406, 2/2/1995 (Drawer 174, Folder 2, Page 19)
        - 03450-38A: Arch Precast Drawings: PC-004.1, 004.2, 350, 375, 413-414, 11/1/1995 (Drawer 174, Folder 2, Page 20)
        - 03450-39A: Arch Precast Drawings: PC-361, 361.1, 412, 415, 11/09/1995 (Drawer 174, Folder 2, Page 21)
        - 03450-40A: Arch Precast Drawings: PC-205, 365, 366, 413, 416, 10/26/1995 (Drawer 174, Folder 2, Page 22)
        - 03450-41A: Arch Precast Drawings: PC-216, 217, 350.1, 356.2, 356.3, 12/20/1995 (Drawer 174, Folder 2, Page 23)
      - 03450-42A Hacko, 2-3/1996 (Box 2, Folder 27)
        - 03450-42A: Arch Precast Drawings: PC-004.5, 218, 219-221, 1/10/1996 (Drawer 174, Folder 2, Page 24)
  - Division 04: Masonry
    - 04212
      - 04212-01A: Veazey, 5/1995 (Box 1, Folder 28)
      - 04212-02A-C: Chamberlin, 6/1995 (Box 1, Folder 29)
      - 04212-03A-12A: Veazy, 11/1995 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - 04222
      - 04222-01A: Veazy, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 31)
      - 04222-02A: Veazy, 6-8/1995 (Box 2, Folder 32)
      - 04222-02B: Veazy, 8-9/1995 (Box 2, Folder 33)
      - 04222-02C: Veazy, 9/1995 (Box 2, Folder 34)
      - 04222-02D: Veazy, 11/1995 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Division 05: Metals
    - 05120
      - 05120-01A: Regional, 8-9/1995 (Box 2, Folder 36)
        - Job 268, Drawing EW1 of 2, 7/26/1995 (Drawer 174, Folder 3, Page 1)
        - Job 268, Drawing EW2 of 2, 7/26/1995 (Drawer 174, Folder 3, Page 2)
        - Job 268, Drawing W1 of 2, 7/26/1995 (Drawer 174, Folder 3, Page 3)
        - Job 268, Drawing W2 of 2, 7/26/1995 (Drawer 174, Folder 3, Page 4)
        - Job 268, Drawing F1 of 1, 7/26/1995 (Drawer 174, Folder 3, Page 5)
      - 05120-02A: Regional, 8/1995 (Box 2, Folder 37)
      - 05120-03A: Regional, 8/1995 (Box 2, Folder 38)
      - 05120-04A: Regional, 9/1995 (Box 2, Folder 39)
      - 05120-04B: Regional, 9/1995 (Box 2, Folder 40)
        - Drawing EW3 of 3, 8/15/1995 (Drawer 174, Folder 3, Page 6)
        - Drawing W3-W6, 8/15/1995 (Drawer 174, Folder 3, Page 7-10)
      - 05120-05A: Regional, 9/1995 (Box 2, Folder 41)
      - 05120-06A: Regional, 9/1995 (Box 2, Folder 42)
        - S3.05, Roof Plan, 4/11/1995 (Drawer 174, Folder 3, Page 10a)
        - S5.01, Roof Typical Details, 12/22/1994 (Drawer 174, Folder 3, Page 10b)
        - S5.02, Roof Details, 4/11/1995 (Drawer 174, Folder 3, Page 10c)
        - S5.03, Roof Details, 4/11/1995 (Drawer 174, Folder 3, Page 10d)
        - S5.10, Brace Frame and Details, 12/22/1994 (Drawer 174, Folder 3, Page 10e)
        - S/O NO. 268, Sheet 55-59, 8/18/1995 (Drawer 174, Folder 3, Page 10f-10j)
        - S/O NO. 268, Sheet 65-76, 8/18/1995 (Drawer 174, Folder 3, Page 10k-10v)
        - S/O NO. 268, Sheet 81-83, 8/18/1995 (Drawer 174, Folder 3, Page 10w-10y)
      - 05120-07A: Regional, 10/1995 (Box 2, Folder 43)
      - 05120-08A: Regional, 11/1995 (Box 2, Folder 44)
        - Drawing E7, 10/18/1995 (Drawer 174, Folder 3, Page 11)
        - Sheet 77-80, 84-86, 87 (2 copies), 88, 8/1/1995 (Drawer 174, Folder 3, Page 12-21)
      - 05120-09A: International Precast and Steel Erectors, 12/1995 (Box 2, Folder 45)
      - 05120-10A Lott Builders, 12/1995 (Box 2, Folder 46)
      - 05120-11A: International Precast and Steel Erectors, 2/1996 (Box 2, Folder 47)
      - 05120-12A: Regional, 6/1996 (Box 2, Folder 48)
        - Sheet 88, 5/13/1996 (Drawer 174, Folder 3, Page 22)
    - 05200
      - 05200-01A: Regional Constructions, 9/1995 (Box 2, Folder 49)
      - 05200-01B: Regional Constructions, 11/1995 (Box 2, Folder 50)
      - 05200-02A: Regional Constructions, 9/1995 (Box 2, Folder 51)
        - Drawing V1 of 4, 8/1/1995 (Drawer 174, Folder 3, Page 23)
        - Drawing D1 of 3, 8/1/1995 (Drawer 174, Folder 3, Page 24)
        - Drawing V2 of 4, 8/1/1995 (Drawer 174, Folder 3, Page 25)
        - Drawing V2 of 3, 8/1/1995 (Drawer 174, Folder 3, Page 26)
        - Drawing V3 of 4, 8/1/1995 (Drawer 174, Folder 3, Page 27)
        - Drawing D3 of 4, 8/1/1995 (Drawer 174, Folder 3, Page 28)
        - Drawing V4 of 4, 8/1/1995 (Drawer 174, Folder 3, Page 29)
      - 05200-02B: Regional Constructions, 11/1995 (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - 05400
      - 05400-01A: Marek Brothers Systems, Inc., 10/1995 (Box 2, Folder 53)
      - 05400-01B: Marek Brothers Systems, Inc., 11/1995 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - 05510
      - 05510-01A: Regional, 9/1995 (Box 2, Folder 55)
        - Stairs A, B, C, Sheets 1-7, 8/9/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 1, Page 1-7)
      - 05510-01B: Regional, 11/1995 (Box 2, Folder 56)
      - 05510-02A: Regional, 8/24/1995 (Box 2, Folder 57)
        - Material Sample, 8/24/1995 (Box 16, Folder 2)
      - 05510-03A: Regional, 9/1995 (Box 2, Folder 58)
        - Sheet W3 of 3, 9/8/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 1, Page 8)
        - Drawing EW3 of 3, 9/8/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 1, Page 9)
      - 05510-03B: Regional, 12/1995 (Box 2, Folder 59)
        - Sheet 5 of 51, 10/22/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 1, Page 10)
        - Sheet 12 of 51, 10/22/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 1, Page 11)
        - Sheet 44 of 51, 10/22/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 1, Page 12)
      - 05510-04A: Regional, 11/1995 (Box 2, Folder 60)
      - 05510-05A: Regional, 12/1995 (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - 05700
      - 05700-01A: Offenhauser, 6/1995 (Box 2, Folder 62)
        - Drawing OE1, 2/2/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 1, Page 13)
        - Drawing O1-1, 2/2/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 1, Page 14)
        - Drawing O6-E1, 2/2/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 1, Page 15)
        - Drawing O6-1, 2/2/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 1, Page 16)
        - Drawing O6-2, 2/2/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 1, Page 17)
        - Drawing OE2, 2/2/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 1, Page 18)
        - Drawing OE3, 2/2/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 1, Page 19)
        - Drawing O7-1, 2/2/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 1, Page 20)
        - Drawing O12-1, 2/2/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 1, Page 21)
      - 05700-01B: Offenhauser, 9/1995 (Box 2, Folder 63)
        - Drawing O1-1, 10/22/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 1, Page 22)
        - Drawing OE-1, 10/22/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 1, Page 23)
      - 05700-01C: Offenhauser, 7-8/1996 (Box 2, Folder 64)
        - Drawing O6-1A, Sheet 1 of 5, 7/12/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 1, Page 24)
        - Drawing O6-1B, Sheet 2 of 5, 7/12/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 1, Page 25)
        - Drawing O6-2A, Sheet 3 of 5, 7/12/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 1, Page 26)
        - Drawing O6-1B, Sheet 4 of 5, 7/12/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 1, Page 27)
        - Drawing O6-2C, Sheet 5 of 5, 7/12/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 1, Page 28)
      - 05700-01D: Offenhauser, 9-10/1996 (Box 2, Folder 65)
        - Drawing 06-1A, 8/27/1996 (Drawer 175, Folder 1, Page 29)
        - Drawing 06-1B, 8/27/1996 (Drawer 175, Folder 1, Page 30)
        - Drawing 06-2A, 8/27/1996 (Drawer 175, Folder 1, Page 31)
        - Drawing 06-2B, 8/27/1996 (Drawer 175, Folder 1, Page 32)
        - Drawing 06-2C, 8/27/1996 (Drawer 175, Folder 1, Page 33)
        - Drawing 06-2D, 8/27/1996 (Drawer 175, Folder 1, Page 34)
      - 05700-02A: Offenhauser, 1/1996 (Box 2, Folder 66)
      - 05700-02B: Offenhauser, 2/1996 (Box 2, Folder 67)
      - 05700-03A: Offenhauser, 1/1996 (Box 2, Folder 68)
      - 05700-04A: Offenhauser, 1/1996 (Box 2, Folder 69)
        - Drawing 5.1, 1/12/1996 (Drawer 175, Folder 1, Page 35)
        - Drawing 5.2, 1/12/1996 (Drawer 175, Folder 1, Page 36)
        - Drawing 5.1, 1/16/1996 (Drawer 175, Folder 1, Page 37)
        - Drawing 5.2, 1/16/1996 (Drawer 175, Folder 1, Page 38)
      - 05700-04B: Offenhauser, 2/1996 (Box 2, Folder 70)
      - 05700-05A-09A: Offenhauser, 1/1996-3/1996 (Box 2, Folder 71)
      - 05700-09B: Offenhauser, 4/1996 (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - 05999
      - 05999-01A: Regional, 9/1995 (Box 2, Folder 73)
      - 05999-01B: Regional, 12/1995 (Box 2, Folder 74)
        - Sheet 77-80, 84-87, 11/21/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 1, Page 39-46)
      - 05999-02A: Regional, 10/1995 (Box 2, Folder 75)
      - 05999-02B: Regional, 5/1995 (Box 2, Folder 76)
        - Sheet 88, 5/13/1996 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 1)
      - 05999-03A: Regional, 2/1996 (Box 2, Folder 77)
        - Sheet 22, 1/24/1996 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 2)
        - Sheet 22, 2/6/1996 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 3)
      - 05999-03B: Regional, 2/1996 (Box 2, Folder 78)
        - Sheet 22, 2/12/1996 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 4)
      - 05999-04A: Regional, 6/1996 (Box 2, Folder 79)
        - Sheet 30, 6/1996 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 5)
        - Sheet 31, 6/1996 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 6)
        - Sheet E100, 6/1996 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 7)
  - Division 06: Wood and Plastics
    - 06410
    - 06400
  - Division 07: Thermal and Moisture Protection
    - 07120
      - 07120-01A-01C, Chamberlin, 6/1995-9/1995 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - 07130
      - 07130-01A, Chamberlin, 3/1995 (Box 3, Folder 2)
      - 07130-02A-02B, Chamberlin, 8/1995 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - 07140
      - 07140-01A-01B, Chamberlin, 6/1995 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - 07160
      - 07160-01A, Chamberlin, 6/1996 (Box 3, Folder 5)
      - 07160-02A-02B, Chamberlin, 11/1995 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - 07200
      - 07200-01A-03A, Gulf Star, 11/1995-12/1995 (Box 3, Folder 7)
      - 07200-04A-11A, Ryder Co., 12/1995 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - 07270
      - 07250-01A, Diversified Thermal, 12/1995 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - 07250
      - 07270-01A, MLN Co., 12/1995 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - 07320
      - 07320-01A-01B, Gulf Star, 11/1995-3/1996 (Box 3, Folder 11)
      - 07320-02A, Gulf Star, 12/1995 (Box 3, Folder 12)
      - 07320-03B, Gulf Star, 2/1996 (Box 3, Folder 13)
      - 07320-03A-05B, Gulf Star, 11/1995-12/1995 (Box 3, Folder 14)
        - 07320-03A, Drawing 1 of 4, 11/22/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 8)
        - 07320-03A, Drawing 2 of 4, 11/22/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 9)
        - 07320-03A, Drawing 3 of 4, 11/22/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 10)
        - 07320-03A, Drawing 4 of 4, 11/22/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 11)
        - 07320-03A, Drawing 1 of 4, 12/13/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 12)
        - 07320-03A, Drawing 2 of 4, 12/13/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 13)
        - 07320-03A, Drawing 3 of 4, 12/13/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 14)
        - 07320-03A, Drawing 4 of 4, 12/13/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 15)
        - 07320-03B, 1 of 4, 2/22/1996 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 16)
        - 07320-03B, 2 of 4, 2/22/1996 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 17)
        - 07320-03B, 3 of 4, 2/22/1996 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 18)
        - 07320-03B, 4 of 4, 2/22/1996 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 19)
    - 07410
      - 07410-01A; 01C, Gulf Star, 11/1995 (Box 3, Folder 15)
      - 07410-02A-03A, Gulf Star, 1/1996 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - 07525
      - 07525-01A-03A, Chamberlin, 10/1995, 1/1996 (Box 3, Folder 17)
      - 07525-04A-10A, Chamberlin, 1/1996 (Box 3, Folder 18)
      - 07525-11A-13A, Chamberlin, 1/1996-2/1996 (Box 3, Folder 19)
      - 07525-14A, Lott, 8/1996 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - 07600
      - 07600-01A-04A, Chamberlin, 6/1995-2/1996 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - 07724